Let's chase our dreams...
... holding hearts burning...
... like the summer sunshine.
If we have courage...
... at 100 miles an hour...
... l'm sure the door will open.
Since sadness is the road
that leads to smiles...
... dull, dingy shoes will
start to shine, too.
The most wonderful dream
in the world...
The poundingbeat speeds up.
The eyes are prisms that
catch the wind...
... and in the voices of
countless friends...
... I feel happiness.
Regarding the matter at hand,
I hope to hear from you soon.
Understood, Sir. I'll look
into it right away.
Oh, could you unload your Moto-Compo?
I'm going to check it out after lunch.
Riiight...
Look, you couldn't
help it!
The GSX has a lot more power
than your Moto-Compo.
Right, why don't we go and have a
chat with the folks at the DMV?
At the very least, your
license is history!
Nakajima, thanks!
I owe you one!
Don't mention it... I happened to be
in the neighborhood. Lucky, eh?
You're a big help.
Oh, working hard, I see!
Where's Tsujimoto?
Huh? Natsumi is right h...
Huh?!
Oh, gee, am I bummed!
That Miyuki... All she said was,
"You couldn't help it!"
Don't you think that was
uncalled for? 'Cause...
...my Moto-Compo makes up for its lack
of power with superior maneuverability!
Doesn't it, Oshou?
If the race always goes to the biggest
and fastest, then we're history!
It really sucks big time!
'Cause we won't be able
to make enough busts!
In other words, you're jealous
of the White Bike Troopers.
Eh? I didn't know you'd been
adopted by the Temple...
Hmm..."Jealous," eh?
Maybe I am.
But, what really pisses me off is the way
Miyuki tried to make me feel better!
Isn't that called "defeatism?"
Isn't it?
Thank you very much
for the tea...
...and for listening to me spill my
guts. I feel much better, Oshou!
Well, I'm glad.
Hello!
Long time no see, Sir.
Chief!
My! You haven't
changed a bit!
Why don't you have a seat, and
I'll get you a cup of tea.
Er... You know Oshou?
Uh-huh. He's my mentor.
M... Mentor?!
He was a policeman for many
years. Also, he's my uncle.
Eh? Your uncle?!
Excuse me...
Chief?
Sheesh! I keep telling him, "Let me
know when the guest leaves!"
A Female...
...White Bike Trooper?!
You want ME to be one?!
That's right. If you'd rather recommend
someone else, then I'll consider it...
...but I can't think of anyone better
qualified than you, Tsujimoto.
I'll do it! I'll do it! Please,
let me do it!
Is that so? In that case, I'll send my
recommendation to Headquarters.
Headquarters?!
Yes... you'll be reporting
to Headquarters.
Wh... Then, I'll have
to transfer?
I'm not asking you to give me
a definite answer right now.
Why don't you take your time
and think it over?
"Take my time?"
If you can let me know your decision by
the end of the week, that'll be fine.
B... By the end
of the week?
Natsumi!
Er... Yes?
Lunch break was over
five minutes ago!
But, never mind that... Come
and check this out.
I've been tinkering with the Moto-Compo.
It should burn a little different...
Wh... What for?
I thought that it could use
a little more power.
Natsumi...
What is it?
I'm sorry about what I said earlier.
It was very inconsiderate of me...
Is that why you were working
on the bike?
Yes, but wouldn't you want to keep
it in top condition all the time?
Oh! Natsumi!
Wh... Wh... What
did I say?!
Wakaba Preschool
School Play
Be sure to come see us perform
"The Rocky Mountain!"
I'll be the mischievous Tanuki.
I'm the Old Man!
I'm the Old Lady!
I'm the Bunny!
I'm Soup!
Sorry. I can't make
it this time.
What?! Why?!
Why?!
Alright!
Maybe tomorrow...
I don't feel like I've
eaten anything.
It seems like my appetite gets worse
every day. What a bummer...
Ah. So that's how it is?
All I can tell you is this...
It's far better to try something
and regret it...
...than to not try something
and regret that...
Chances like this come to you
only if you make them...
...and you have to make the best
of them when you get them.
You're right.
Want me to tell
her for you?
Nah.
I'll tell her myself.
If I were Miyuki...
...l'd wanna be told
directly, I'm sure.
I figured you'd
say that.
Miyuki also wants to be told directly
how you feel about her, Nakajima!
Wh... Why are you bringing
that up?!
'Cause, if I do become
a Trooper...
...then I won't be a member of
Bokuto Precinct, remember?
I won't be able to solve all your
problems long-distance!
Don't you care, Miyuki?
If you don't do anything,
she'll leave!
I know all about it,
you know!
How you busted your butt making
a dossier on Natsumi...
...when you first heard that she'd
be transferring to our station!
And how, on her first day, you
even went out to pick her up!
I remember you said, "Oh, that Natsumi!
She's so late getting here!"
It's done!
Aw, c'mon, Miyuki!
Umm... Miyuki? Can I
talk to you for a sec?
Here you go!
What's this?
A going-away present for you.
You'll be living in
the dorm, right?
That alarm clock is guaranteed
to prevent oversleeping!
How long have you known?
Since you went out to lunch
by yourself at the temple.
You're cruel... You should've
said something.
Maybe you're right.
Hey, I bet this'll electrocute
me or explode, right?
"Hang in there, Tsujimoto!"
Just for you, because you
are a fan of the Chief...
...I obtained five voice samples
of the man himself!
What do you think? With this,
you will rise and shine!
Don't break it, okay? It took a
while to make, you know?
I'm not rational like Miyuki! I'll be
blunt; I don't want you to go!
Aw, it's okay! I will be back,
so be a good girl, okay?
Letter of
Recommendation
You can't even balance for 10 seconds?!
What're you gonna do?!
Tsujimoto! You can get
off the plank now.
What?!
You're holding up
the whole line!
Riiight...
Hey!
Huh?
Listen, Tsujimoto...
The others are here to learn how
to control their motorcycles.
You, on the other hand, ought to learn
how to control yourself! Got that?!
Eeeeuuuuuuh!
This is Patrol School. We don't "Eeuuh"
here. It's "Yes, Sir!" Got that?!
Yessir...
Don't let him get to you... You've
got natural talent, Tsujimoto.
But, for some reason, I'm not
so confident anymore...
Let's hang in there!
Yeah... I guess...
Uh-oh!
We've got to get going soon,
Nats... I mean, Yoriko!
Right...
Do you think Natsumi's
staying healthy?
Yeah. I'm pretty sure.
Are you worried?
You think she's
doing well?
Of course. It's Natsumi we're
talking about, you know?
What about you,
Miyuki?
Are you doing
all right?
Well, I hope I'm doing as
good a job as she is.
"What's wrong, Tsujimoto?"
Riiight, Chief... I'm
hangin' in there...
Where are your
manners?!
You won't get away
from me!
The guy's crazy!
Oh, no! Natsumi! Your
Foot Brakes!
I can't do anything
like that!
What's the matter? Aren't
you going inside?
Ha ha... for some reason, I'm
kinda embarrassed to!
Is today your day off?
Yes.
They've decided to let me make
my debut as a Trooper...
...so I guess I'm here to let you know,
or maybe just to say hello.
Oh! That's great,
isn't it?!
Yeah, well, I guess.
Well, come in!
And... Howdy!
Umm... Natsumi?
Lookin' good!
Sure could use your
help around here...
The cafeteria lady was saying that sales
are way down since you left!
Where's Miyuki? Is she
in the garage again?
Well...
Tsujimoto!
How is she?
The way I look at it, the damage
could have been much worse.
Yeah.
Still, I guess I'm still not used to
being without you, Natsumi...
Well, you live and learn.
Hey... maybe I should
come back here.
What?!
Ha ha!
W... What are you
talking about?!
It's not like you, Natsumi, to quit
after deciding to do something!
R... Right.
Y... Yeah! Besides, aren't you gonna
be riding escort for the marathon?
Well, that's terrific! You've got
to go and strut your stuff!
Well, it's only a half-marathon...
I just don't understand why
you're acting so wimpy...
...when I've been trying to be as
strong as you always were...
WHY, YOU!
Sob!
What're you doing with
the Moto-Compo?!
Weren't you talking things over
with Tsujimoto just now?
I thought that I'd put it away
in the warehouse.
Put it away?! Why would
you want to do that?!
Wait... What happened?!
Natsumi was saying... that
she might come back.
What?
Because I wasn't...
Because I wasn't strong enough,
I made her say such a thing...
That's not true!
'Cause...
...for her to say such a thing,
it must be the case!
I haven't had the strength to try to
get used to being without her.
You don't need to put the bike away.
There's no reason to put it away...
"Bokuto District Half-Marathon
Grand Prix"
As you can see, the course
follows a 21km path.
Our station will be responsible for
regulating traffic in the vicinity.
We can expect that traffic will
be heavily congested.
This won't be a cakewalk, so be
prepared... and good luck!
Aye, Sir!
Let's get rolling!
Starting gun in 20 seconds.
Finally. Let's relax and
enjoy ourselves.
I already made a pitstop,
so I'm hunky-dory!
10 seconds...
On your marks...
We're sorry, but this route
will be closed until 3 P. M!
There she is!
She's here! She's here!
Natsumi! Over here!
I'm the Old Man!
I'm the Tanuki!
Old Lady here!
Soup!
Bunny!
Rocky Mountain!
Sheesh! That was it?!
Mega-boring!
That's weird... Out
of gas already?!
Tsujimoto, you're going too fast!
Oops!
Yoriko, hurry!
What is it?! What's
going on?
A vehicle on fire! And it couldn't
have happened at a worse time!
What the hell do you
think you're doing?!
Back up, man!
Can't you see that's dangerous?!
There it is!
Radio for assistance!
I'll try to re-direct the cars!
Please back up slowly! Don't rush!
Back up slowly!
Your cooperation is greatly
appreciated!
Say what? I can't
hear you very well.
In flames?! A truck?!
Yoriko, calm down and
give me the location!
Okay, gotcha! I'll be
right there!
Stay on top on what's happening
on the streets.
We must keep the spectators
from panicking.
Roger!
We may have a problem here...
A fire?! At a time
like this?!
Hold a sec... Lemme check
it out with Headquarters!
Miyuki! Over here!
Gee! At a time like this, if Natsumi
were here, she'd just...
NO WAY!
But...
Sorry...
We've got to hurry!
What're you gonna do?
I'm getting the car!
Don't tell me...
I knew it!
In this kind of situation, who cares
about a few dents and scratches?
Anyone injured? And how many
officers are en route?
They cut me off!
Tsujimoto... your face!
We escorts shouldn't look
like we're in a bad mood!
How 'bout this?!
Yo, Yoriko, how's
it going?
Nakajima! The fire trucks can't get
here because of all the cars!
Damn! We won't be able to do anything
to stop this kind of fire!
Damn! Hold your breath!
Gotta retreat for
the time being!
To the Kitten with a Beautiful
Smile... This is the Fox.
H... Hold on! How on Earth
do you know all this?
I've told you what
I know.
The rest is up to you.
I wish you the best.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry...
...but please handle things
from here on!
Tsujimoto!
Aw, just when we were
able to see her...
It's Natsumi!
Natsumi!
Bye-bye!
Natsumi! Cool! Awesome!
Yoriko... How are
you doing?
I'm not dead yet.
We took care of moving the cars.
Now all we need is a fire truck.
Thanks. I owe you
another one...
Kobayakawa, Nakajima...
Well done.
The fire truck should
arrive very soon.
What about the Marathon?
It's running smoothly.
Thank goodness.
Like I've told you already, the road's
blocked off; I can't get through!
Look, you aren't the only one
inconvenienced by this!
Oh... Nakajima!
Wh... What the?!
Yoriko! Put your
seat belt on!
What is it? What's
goin' on?!
It doesn't look like Nakajima
can get in there!
We've got to do something!
Oh!
Natsumi!
Let's stop that thing NOW!
Tsujimoto!
This thing is too heavy! We're
not going to stop!
Natsumi! Put it
in reverse!
H... How am I supposed to do that?!
Calm down! I'll tell you how!
First, apply the side brakes
to lock the rear wheels!
Gotcha!
Step on the clutch, then shift
into reverse!
Step off the clutch... Release
the side brakes...
...and FLOOR IT!
Stop, dammit!
Tsujimoto!
Note: She is doing the hand gesture for "sorry."
Sakai... I'd better give
this back to you.
Eh?
You're gonna quit,
aren't you?
I realized that I don't belong on
a fixed route, that's why.
A perfect 10!
Huh?
Your smile was excellent!
That was the best I've
ever seen you make!
You sure about this?
You're the one
who told me...
"Chances like this come to you
only if you make them...
"...and you have to make the best of
them when you get them." Right?
So I hear she pulled yet another
impulsive stunt, huh?
It's so like her.
Yo! Is the seat next
to you taken?
Yo, girlfriend, could I
hitch a ride wit'cha?
Miyuki?
Silly!
Yup! That's me!
I love the smile you always have.
With all the passion I have...
...I will protect you from sighs.
The sunset skyline flashes past
in my side-view mirror.
This is the road I drive on every day,
believing in my dreams.
On rainy days, windy days, and days
when I wanted to throw it all away...
... you smiled as you
sat beside me.
I love the unchanging vista, the sky
that we watch together.
That's why I'm confident that I can
hang in there, if it's for you.
I love the smile you always have.
With all the passion I have...
...I will protect you from sighs.
THE END